781-479-9083 | Lynn, MA | rbell@email.neit.edu

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Dedicated, efficient professional with excellent work ethic. Strong skills in programming. Works well with colleagues in a team environment. Excellent written and verbal communication skills. Analytical thinking. Ability to break down a problem and find the most effective solutions.

- C#, C++, Java
- Fundatmental knowledge and training in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and Python
- Familiarity with Jira, Confluence.
- 3 years of experience with Unity Game-Engine
- 2 years of experience with Mono-Game Framework
- Plastic SCM, Perforce (P4V)
- Vegas Pro

EDUCATION

New England Institute of Technology, East Greenwich, RI Bachelor of Science in Game Development & Simulation Programming | 09/2023

PROJECTS

Punch Back | Unity 2D | Side-Scroll Platformer | March 2021 - Completed

- Collaborated with a colleague to create a game. I served as the Lead Programmer.
- Punch Back was created in 10 weeks, where I was paired with 1 game designer.

LiDAR | Unity 3D | VR Horror Game | August 2022 - In Development

- Collaborated with two colleagues to make a Virtual Reality horror game.
- I was the gameplay and UI programmer. We kept the game updated through Plastic SCM.

The Ristrovik Crisis | Unity 3D HDRP | First-person Horror Game | April 2023 - In Development

• Collaborated with two colleagues to make a 3D first person horror game. I was the gameplay programmer, programming the character controller and most of the main mechanics.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Walmart | Unloader & Stocking | October 2022 - Present | Warwick, RI

- Work closely with the team to help unload trucks efficiently.
- Assist in stocking in various departments the sales floor.

Compass Group | Dishwasher & Cashier | December 2021 - October 2022 | East Greenwich, RI

- Assisted customers. Made sales and answered questions. Maintained strong knowledge of products.
- Collaborated well in a team environment.

Best Buy | Computing Sales Associate | October 2019 - February 2021 | Saugus, MA

- Assisted customers in the purchase of computers and similar products.
- Maintained strong knowledge of computers and peripherals. Ensured department was properly stocked.